CARLO BONILLA MORALES

Alajuela · +506 85011597

carlobonilla640@gmail.com · Carlo Bonilla · Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/carlo-bonilla-b6a67623a/

Hello, my Full name is Carlo Alejandro Bonilla Morales. I live in Alajuela. I like to be researching the news about my career. That's why I like being self-taught. My English level is A2+

WORK EXPERIENCE

I have basic Knowledge of sql server management and the following programming languages.

	Mayo 2021 – diciembre 2021
 	JAVA Developer Developed desktop applications with java in college.
	Enero 2022 – abril 2022
 	C# Developer Developed desktop applications with C# in college.
 	Mayo 2022 – agosto 2022
 	HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Web Developer Developed web applications with javascript, html and css a bit of react, bootstrap 5
i	Septiembre 2022 – diciembre 2022
 	JAVA Web Developer Developed web applications with JAVA, html, css and bootstrap 5.
	Enero 2023 – Currently
	C# Web Developer with .NET ASP Developed web applications with C#, html, css and bootstrap 5.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

```
2021 - Currently

Universidad Técnica Nacional de Costa Rica
Diploma

2013 - 2019

High School CTP de Sabalito
Diploma
```

SKILLS

- Initiative
- Team Work
- Leadership

- Creative
- Respectful
- Responsible